WJZ-TV Collection R0129.WJZ R0129.WJZ
Stage
- Evening Magazine, 1977-1991; EVMAG; 8 Reels 2 inch videotape: Quad; 4,676 Cassettes
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-11-13; WJZ-EVMAG-073-014 (Mixed materials 73, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-11-14; WJZ-EVMAG-073-015 (Mixed materials 73, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-11-14-1980-11-17; WJZ-EVMAG-073-016 (Mixed materials 73, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-11-17-1980-11-24; WJZ-EVMAG-073-017 (Mixed materials 73, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12; WJZ-EVMAG-075-001 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-02; WJZ-EVMAG-075-002 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-04-1980-12-05; WJZ-EVMAG-075-003 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-05; WJZ-EVMAG-075-004 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-05-1980-12-08; WJZ-EVMAG-075-005 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-08-1980-12-09; WJZ-EVMAG-075-006 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-09; WJZ-EVMAG-075-007 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-10-1980-12-11; WJZ-EVMAG-075-008 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-11; WJZ-EVMAG-075-009 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-10-1980-12-16; WJZ-EVMAG-075-010 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-12-1980-12-19; WJZ-EVMAG-075-011 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-16-1980-12-17; WJZ-EVMAG-075-012 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-18; WJZ-EVMAG-075-013 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-12-19; WJZ-EVMAG-075-014 (Mixed materials 75, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-17-1981-03-18; WJZ-EVMAG-081-001 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-17-1981-03-20; WJZ-EVMAG-081-002 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-23-1981-03-24; WJZ-EVMAG-081-003 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-19; WJZ-EVMAG-081-004 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-19-1981-03-20; WJZ-EVMAG-081-005 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-22-1981-03-23; WJZ-EVMAG-081-006 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-23-1981-03-26; WJZ-EVMAG-081-007 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-24; WJZ-EVMAG-081-008 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-24; WJZ-EVMAG-081-009 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-02-25-1981-03-26; WJZ-EVMAG-081-010 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-26; WJZ-EVMAG-081-011 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-27; WJZ-EVMAG-081-012 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-27-1981-04-03; WJZ-EVMAG-081-013 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-27-1981-03-30; WJZ-EVMAG-081-014 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-30-1981-04-27; WJZ-EVMAG-081-015 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-31-1981-04-01; WJZ-EVMAG-081-016 (Mixed materials 81, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-31-1981-04-02; WJZ-EVMAG-082-001 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-01; WJZ-EVMAG-082-002 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-02; WJZ-EVMAG-082-003 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-02; WJZ-EVMAG-082-004 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-02-1981-04-03; WJZ-EVMAG-082-005 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-06; WJZ-EVMAG-082-006 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-07; WJZ-EVMAG-082-007 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-08; WJZ-EVMAG-082-008 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-08-1981-04-09; WJZ-EVMAG-082-009 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-09; WJZ-EVMAG-082-010 (Mixed materials 82, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-15-1981-04-23; WJZ-EVMAG-083-001 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-16-1981-04-17; WJZ-EVMAG-083-002 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-20; WJZ-EVMAG-083-003 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-20-1981-04-21; WJZ-EVMAG-083-004 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-21; WJZ-EVMAG-083-005 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-21-1981-05-06; WJZ-EVMAG-083-006 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-22; WJZ-EVMAG-083-007 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-22-1981-04-23; WJZ-EVMAG-083-008 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-24; WJZ-EVMAG-083-009 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-24-1981-04-27; WJZ-EVMAG-083-010 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-27-1981-04-29; WJZ-EVMAG-083-011 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-28; WJZ-EVMAG-083-012 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-28-1981-04-29; WJZ-EVMAG-083-013 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-29; WJZ-EVMAG-083-014 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-30; WJZ-EVMAG-083-015 (Mixed materials 83, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-04-30-1981-05-02; WJZ-EVMAG-084-001 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-01; WJZ-EVMAG-084-002 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-04; WJZ-EVMAG-084-003 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-04-1981-05-05; WJZ-EVMAG-084-004 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-05; WJZ-EVMAG-084-005 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-06; WJZ-EVMAG-084-006 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-06-1981-05-07; WJZ-EVMAG-084-007 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-05-1981-05-15; WJZ-EVMAG-084-008 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-08; WJZ-EVMAG-084-009 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-08; WJZ-EVMAG-084-010 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-08-1981-05-11; WJZ-EVMAG-084-011 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-11-1981-05-27; WJZ-EVMAG-084-012 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-12-1981-05-13; WJZ-EVMAG-084-013 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-12-1981-05-18; WJZ-EVMAG-084-014 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-14; WJZ-EVMAG-084-015 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-15; WJZ-EVMAG-084-016 (Mixed materials 84, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-14-1981-05-15; WJZ-EVMAG-085-001 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-19-1981-06-02; WJZ-EVMAG-085-002 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-18; WJZ-EVMAG-085-003 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-19-1981-05-20; WJZ-EVMAG-085-004 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-20; WJZ-EVMAG-085-005 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-21; WJZ-EVMAG-085-006 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-21-1981-05-22; WJZ-EVMAG-085-007 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-21-1981-06-08; WJZ-EVMAG-085-008 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-22; WJZ-EVMAG-085-009 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-23; WJZ-EVMAG-085-010 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-25-1981-05-28; WJZ-EVMAG-085-011 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-26; WJZ-EVMAG-085-012 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-27; WJZ-EVMAG-085-013 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-28-1981-06-15; WJZ-EVMAG-085-014 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-05-29-1981-06-01; WJZ-EVMAG-085-015 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-06-02-1981-06-03; WJZ-EVMAG-085-016 (Mixed materials 85, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-06-03-1981-06-09; WJZ-EVMAG-086-001 (Mixed materials 86, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-06-04-1981-06-05; WJZ-EVMAG-086-002 (Mixed materials 86, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-06-10; WJZ-EVMAG-086-003 (Mixed materials 86, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-07-23-1981-08-14; WJZ-EVMAG-087-002 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-07-24; WJZ-EVMAG-087-003 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-07-24-1981-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-087-004 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-07-27-1981-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-087-005 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-08; WJZ-EVMAG-087-006 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-08-03-1981-08-05; WJZ-EVMAG-087-007 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-08-07; WJZ-EVMAG-087-008 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-08-10; WJZ-EVMAG-087-009 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-08-10; WJZ-EVMAG-087-010 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-08-18; WJZ-EVMAG-087-011 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-08-21-1981-08-26; WJZ-EVMAG-087-012 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-08-28-1981-09-02; WJZ-EVMAG-087-013 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-09; WJZ-EVMAG-087-014 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-09; WJZ-EVMAG-087-015 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-09-03-1981-09-14; WJZ-EVMAG-087-016 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-08-27-1981-09-08; WJZ-EVMAG-087-017 (Mixed materials 87, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-09; WJZ-EVMAG-088-001 (Mixed materials 88, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-09-15-1981-09-24; WJZ-EVMAG-088-002 (Mixed materials 88, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-12-16; WJZ-EVMAG-089-001 (Mixed materials 89, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-12-29-1982-01-15; WJZ-EVMAG-089-002 (Mixed materials 89, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1982-01-05; WJZ-EVMAG-089-003 (Mixed materials 89, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1982-10-13; WJZ-EVMAG-090-001 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1982-10-21; WJZ-EVMAG-090-002 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1982-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-090-003 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1982-10-26; WJZ-EVMAG-090-004 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1982-10-28; WJZ-EVMAG-090-005 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-05-16-1983-05-17; WJZ-EVMAG-091-001 (Mixed materials 91, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-05-18-1983-06-28; WJZ-EVMAG-091-002 (Mixed materials 91, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-08-04-1983-08-12; WJZ-EVMAG-091-003 (Mixed materials 91, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-12-13; WJZ-EVMAG-092-001 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-12-14-1983-12-15; WJZ-EVMAG-092-002 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-12-16-1983-12-19; WJZ-EVMAG-092-003 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-12-20-1983-12-21; WJZ-EVMAG-092-004 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-12-22; WJZ-EVMAG-092-005 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-12-26; WJZ-EVMAG-092-006 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-12-27-1983-12-28; WJZ-EVMAG-092-007 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1983-12-29-1983-12-30; WJZ-EVMAG-092-008 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984; WJZ-EVMAG-092-009 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-01-02-1984-01-03; WJZ-EVMAG-092-010 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-092-011 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-01-04-1984-01-05; WJZ-EVMAG-092-012 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-01-10-1984-01-11; WJZ-EVMAG-092-013 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-01-12-1984-01-13; WJZ-EVMAG-092-014 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-01-16-1984-01-17; WJZ-EVMAG-092-015 (Mixed materials 92, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-14; WJZ-EVMAG-094-001 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-14-1984-03-15; WJZ-EVMAG-094-002 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-16-1984-03-19; WJZ-EVMAG-094-003 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-21-1984-03-22; WJZ-EVMAG-094-004 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-23-1984-03-26; WJZ-EVMAG-094-005 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-27-1984-03-28; WJZ-EVMAG-094-006 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-29-1984-03-30; WJZ-EVMAG-094-007 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-29; WJZ-EVMAG-094-008 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-02; WJZ-EVMAG-094-009 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-03-1984-04-04; WJZ-EVMAG-094-010 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-05; WJZ-EVMAG-094-011 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-05-1984-04-06; WJZ-EVMAG-094-012 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-10-1984-04-11; WJZ-EVMAG-094-013 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-12-1984-04-13; WJZ-EVMAG-094-014 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-16-1984-04-17; WJZ-EVMAG-094-015 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-18-1984-04-19; WJZ-EVMAG-094-016 (Mixed materials 94, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-07-1984-06-11; WJZ-EVMAG-096-001 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 1)
    - Playgirl's Man of The Year, You Can Look Like Joan Collins, Weekend Guide, Cheerleader, Krazy George, 1984-06-07; WJZ-EVMAG-096-001-01 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 1, Segment 1, Reel 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-12-1984-06-13; WJZ-EVMAG-096-002 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-14-1984-06-15; WJZ-EVMAG-096-003 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-18; WJZ-EVMAG-096-004 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-19; WJZ-EVMAG-096-005 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-19; WJZ-EVMAG-096-006 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-20-1984-06-21; WJZ-EVMAG-096-007 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-22-1984-06-25; WJZ-EVMAG-096-008 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-26-1984-06-27; WJZ-EVMAG-096-009 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-28-1984-06-29; WJZ-EVMAG-096-010 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-02-1984-07-03; WJZ-EVMAG-096-011 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-04-1984-07-05; WJZ-EVMAG-096-012 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-05-1985-07-11; WJZ-EVMAG-096-013 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-096-014 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-06-1984-07-09; WJZ-EVMAG-096-015 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-10-1984-07-11; WJZ-EVMAG-096-016 (Mixed materials 96, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-12-1984-07-13; WJZ-EVMAG-097-001 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-097-002 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-18-1984-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-097-003 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-19-1984-10-04; WJZ-EVMAG-097-004 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-20-1984-07-23; WJZ-EVMAG-097-005 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-24-1984-07-25; WJZ-EVMAG-097-006 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-26-1984-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-097-007 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-08-13-1984-08-14; WJZ-EVMAG-097-008 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-08-15-1984-08-16; WJZ-EVMAG-097-009 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-08-17-1984-08-20; WJZ-EVMAG-097-010 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-08-21-1984-08-22; WJZ-EVMAG-097-011 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-08-23-1984-08-24; WJZ-EVMAG-097-012 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-08-26; WJZ-EVMAG-097-013 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-08-27-1984-08-28; WJZ-EVMAG-097-014 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-08-29-1984-08-30; WJZ-EVMAG-097-015 (Mixed materials 97, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-08-31-1984-09-03; WJZ-EVMAG-098-001 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09; WJZ-EVMAG-098-002 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09; WJZ-EVMAG-098-003 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09; WJZ-EVMAG-098-004 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09-04-1984-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-098-005 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09-06; WJZ-EVMAG-098-006 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09-12-1984-09-13; WJZ-EVMAG-098-007 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09-14-1987-09-17; WJZ-EVMAG-098-008 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09-18-1984-09-19; WJZ-EVMAG-098-009 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09-20-1984-09-21; WJZ-EVMAG-098-010 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09-24-1984-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-098-011 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09-26-1984-09-27; WJZ-EVMAG-098-012 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-09-28; WJZ-EVMAG-098-013 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10; WJZ-EVMAG-098-014 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-01; WJZ-EVMAG-098-015 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-02; WJZ-EVMAG-098-016 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-03-1984-10-04; WJZ-EVMAG-098-017 (Mixed materials 98, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-03-1984-10-31; WJZ-EVMAG-099-001 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-08-1987-01-19; WJZ-EVMAG-099-002 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-09; WJZ-EVMAG-099-003 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-10-1984-10-11; WJZ-EVMAG-099-004 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-12-1984-10-15; WJZ-EVMAG-099-005 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-16-1984-10-17; WJZ-EVMAG-099-006 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-18; WJZ-EVMAG-099-007 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-19; WJZ-EVMAG-099-008 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-19-1984-10-22; WJZ-EVMAG-099-009 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-23-1984-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-099-010 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-25-1984-10-26; WJZ-EVMAG-099-011 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-29-1984-10-30; WJZ-EVMAG-099-012 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-10-31-1984-11-01; WJZ-EVMAG-099-013 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-02-1984-11-05; WJZ-EVMAG-099-014 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-07-1984-11-08; WJZ-EVMAG-099-015 (Mixed materials 99, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-09-1984-11-12; WJZ-EVMAG-100-001 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-13-1984-11-14; WJZ-EVMAG-100-002 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-15-1984-11-16; WJZ-EVMAG-100-003 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-19-1984-11-20; WJZ-EVMAG-100-004 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-21-1984-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-100-005 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-23-1984-11-26; WJZ-EVMAG-100-006 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-27-1984-11-28; WJZ-EVMAG-100-007 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-28; WJZ-EVMAG-100-008 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-11-29-1984-11-30; WJZ-EVMAG-100-009 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-03-1984-12-04; WJZ-EVMAG-100-010 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-05-1984-12-06; WJZ-EVMAG-100-011 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-07-1984-12-10; WJZ-EVMAG-100-012 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-11-1984-12-12; WJZ-EVMAG-100-013 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-13-1984-12-14; WJZ-EVMAG-100-014 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-17-1984-12-18; WJZ-EVMAG-100-015 (Mixed materials 100, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-19-1984-12-20; WJZ-EVMAG-101-001 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-21-1984-12-24; WJZ-EVMAG-101-002 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-25-1984-12-26; WJZ-EVMAG-101-003 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-27-1984-12-28; WJZ-EVMAG-101-004 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-12-31; WJZ-EVMAG-101-005 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985; WJZ-EVMAG-101-006 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985; WJZ-EVMAG-101-007 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985; WJZ-EVMAG-101-008 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985; WJZ-EVMAG-101-009 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01; WJZ-EVMAG-101-010 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-01; WJZ-EVMAG-101-011 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-02-1985-01-03; WJZ-EVMAG-101-012 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-04-1985-01-07; WJZ-EVMAG-101-013 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-08-1985-01-09; WJZ-EVMAG-101-014 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-10-1985-01-11; WJZ-EVMAG-101-015 (Mixed materials 101, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-14-1985-01-15; WJZ-EVMAG-102-001 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-16-1985-01-17; WJZ-EVMAG-102-002 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-18-1985-01-21; WJZ-EVMAG-102-003 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-22-1985-01-23; WJZ-EVMAG-102-004 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-24-1985-01-25; WJZ-EVMAG-102-005 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-28-1985-01-29; WJZ-EVMAG-102-006 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-29; WJZ-EVMAG-102-007 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-29; WJZ-EVMAG-102-008 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-01-30-1985-01-31; WJZ-EVMAG-102-009 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-02-01-1985-02-04; WJZ-EVMAG-102-010 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-02-05-1985-02-06; WJZ-EVMAG-102-011 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-02-07-1985-02-08; WJZ-EVMAG-102-012 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-02-15; WJZ-EVMAG-102-013 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-02-18-1985-02-19; WJZ-EVMAG-102-014 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-02-20-1985-02-21; WJZ-EVMAG-102-015 (Mixed materials 102, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-02-22-1985-02-25; WJZ-EVMAG-103-001 (Mixed materials 103, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-02-26-1985-02-27; WJZ-EVMAG-103-002 (Mixed materials 103, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-02-28; WJZ-EVMAG-103-003 (Mixed materials 103, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-03; WJZ-EVMAG-103-004 (Mixed materials 103, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-03-01; WJZ-EVMAG-103-005 (Mixed materials 103, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-03-04-1985-03-05; WJZ-EVMAG-103-006 (Mixed materials 103, Tape 6)